totalvideogames.com 2001-06-02

# TVG | Privacy Statment

**TVG Privacy Statement**

**Total Video Games Ltd** has created this privacy statement in order to demonstrate our firm commitment to privacy. The following discloses the information gathering and dissemination practices for this Web site: [www.totalvideogames.com](http://www.totalvideogames.com/) / [www.totalentertain.com](http://www.totalentertain.com/) 

##### Advertisers

We use an outside ad company to display ads on our site. These ads may contain cookies. While we use cookies in other parts of our Web site, cookies received with banner ads are collected by our ad company, and we do not have access to this information.

##### Personal Information

General access to the TVG site does not require personal information, however for the myTVG features we require you to register your details with us. We do not sell this information to third parties unless you state in the registration process that you approve us to do so. We will only pass your information onto parties we feel you would like to know information about their products. 

##### External Links

This site contains links to other sites. **TVG** is not responsible for the privacy practices or the content of such Web sites.

##### Public Forums

This site makes chat rooms, forums, message boards, and/or news groups available to its users. Please remember that any information that is disclosed in these areas becomes public information and you should exercise caution when deciding to disclose your personal information.

#### Contacting the Web Site

If you have any questions about this privacy statement, the practices of this site, or your dealings with this Web site, you can contact:
